Hi!
The first thing you need to know about a refrigerator is its overall size.
Is it going to meet your needs adequately.
If it is a remodel and you are going to be doing the cupboards, you need to get the specifications from your contractor to see how wide the opening is as well as the height of the opening also.
If it is brand new construction, you really don't have to worry about that.
So much as you do with your existing construction that is in place already.
Color is another thing that is valuable to know.
What color do you want?
Is it going to match your other appliances?
Or is that not an important feature to you?
Do you want something that has the freezer on top and the fresh fruit area below?
Do you want to bottom out like this with a single swing door on it?